const questions = [
  {
    "id" : 0,
    "question" : "Who is the captian of India ?",
    "options" : [{label : "Sachin", value : 0}, {label : "Dhoni", value : 1}, {label : "Virat", value : 2}],
    "correct_option" : 2
    },
  {
    "id" : 1,
    "question" : "Who is the heightest run getter in ODI ?",
    "options" : [{label : "Sachin", value : 0}, {label : "Lara", value : 1}, {label : "Sachin", value : 2}],
    "correct_option" : 0
    },
  {
    "id" : 2,
    "question" : "Who is the captian of Australia ?",
    "options" : [{label : "Clarke", value : 0}, {label : "Smith", value : 1}, {label : "Warner", value : 2}, {label : "Renshaw", value : 3}],
    "correct_option" : 1
  },
  {
    "id" : 3,
    "question" : "Who is the captian of Pakistan ?",
    "options" : [{label : "Sawfaraz", value : 0}, {label : "Misbah", value : 1}, {label : "Afridi", value : 2}],
    "correct_option" : 0
  },
  {
    "id" : 4,
    "question" : "Who is the coach of India ?",
    "options" : [{label : "John Right", value : 0}, {label : "Ravi Shastri", value : 1}, {label : "Dunkan Fletcher", value : 2}],
    "correct_option" : 1
  },
  {
    "id" : 5,
    "question" : "What is heightest ODI Total ?",
    "options" : [{label : "418", value : 0}, {label : "438", value : 1}, {label : "444", value : 2}],
    "correct_option" : 2
  },
  {
    "id" : 6,
    "question" : "What is heightest Test Total ?",
    "options" : [{label : "960", value : 0}, {label : "902", value : 1}, {label : "850", value : 2}],
    "correct_option" : 0
  },
  {
    "id" : 7,
    "question" : "How many 200 Virat Kohli has ?",
    "options" : [{label : "1", value : 0}, {label : "2", value : 1}, {label : "3", value : 2}, {label : "4", value : 3}],
    "correct_option" : 3
  },
  {
    "id" : 8,
    "question" : "How many 100 Virat Kohli has in ODI ?",
    "options" : [{label : "22", value : 0}, {label : "28", value : 1}, {label : "30", value : 2}, {label : "49", value : 3}],
    "correct_option" : 2
  },
  {
    "id" : 9,
    "question" : "How many 100 Sachin has in ODI ?",
    "options" : [{label : "22", value : 0}, {label : "28", value : 1}, {label : "30", value : 2}, {label : "49", value : 3}],
    "correct_option" : 3
  }
]

export default questions;
